# Jesse Harrah

9730 N K92 Hwy, McLouth, KS 66054 (913) 626-6699 harrahjz@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL, Express and jQuery with a passion for technology and creating meaningful web applications while considering impacts to stakeholders. Highly creative and exceptional problem solver/troubleshooter by nature. Take the initiative to research and learn new languages, frameworks and libraries on my own. Also bring to the table unique and diverse ways to reach a well-thought-out and viable solution to diverse problems and the task at hand. Finally, I am extremely detailed-oriented, excellent at multitasking, a strong analytical and logical thinker, and am highly motivated by the challenge.

## **SKILLS**

- Computer Science applied to JavaScript
- Browser Based Technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)
- Databases (MySQL, MongoDB)
- Server Side Development (Node.js, Express, MERN Stack)
- Deployment (Heroku, Git)
- Java
- Quality Assurance (Writing Tests)
- Internet Marketing (SEO, Semantic HTML)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

BNSF Railway, Kansas City, KS - Journeyman Carman

FEB. 2014 - MAR. 2018

Inspection, repair and maintenance of key railcar equipment/components, including stick & mig welding, torch cutting, plasma arc cutting, metal fabrication. Worked shift-work, weekends and holidays.

**Envirotech Heating & Cooling, Shawnee, KS** - Residential & Commercial HVAC Technician

NOV, 2012 - FEB, 2014

Experience included Sales and repair, maintenance and installation of commercial and residential HVAC equipment/systems, including chillers, boilers, rooftop units and compressor replacements. On-Call 24 hours.

# Samco, Inc., Topeka, KS - Commercial HVAC Technician

MAY, 2012 - JULY, 2012

Repaired, performed maintenance and installed commercial HVAC equipment/systems, including exhaust fans, chillers, freezers, coolers, boilers, rooftop units and compressor replacements.

On-Call 24 hours.

## **EDUCATION**

# University of Kansas Coding Bootcamp, Overland Park, KS - Coding Certificate

(Comprehensive & Condensed 6-month coding bootcamp) APR, 2018 - CURRENT (Estimated completion Oct, 2018)

Washburn Institute of Technology, Topeka, Ks - Electrical & HVAC Certificates AUG, 2010 - MAY, 2012

McLouth High School, McLouth, KS - HS Diploma AUG, 1999 - MAY, 2012

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- EPA Certified
- R410A Certified